A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "ERYTHROMYCIN: Oral erythromycin", 20:94, 1978 October 20 (Box 433, Folder 54-59)
- "ACETAMINOPHEN: Fruit punch with acetaminophen and codeine for children", 20:96, 1978 October 20 (Box 434, Folder 60-64)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Metoprolol (Lopressor)", 20:97, 1978 November 3 (Box 434, Folder 65-70)
- "TRANSPLANTATION: Bone marrow transplantation", 20:98, 1978 November 3 (Box 434, Folder 71-72, Box 435, Folder 73-74)
- "SALICYLATES for RHEUMATISM & ARTHRITIS (CHEMOTHERAPY); Non-aspirin- Salicylates products for arthritis", 20:100, 1978 November 3 (Box 435, Folder 75-79, Box 436, Folder 80-81)
- "SNAKEBITE: Treatment of snakebite in the U.S.A.", 20:101, 1978 November 17 (Box 436, Folder 82-86)
- "LEUKEMIA: Asparaginase", 20:103, 1978 November 17 (Box 436, Folder 87-89, Box 437, Folder 90-92)
- "MEFENAMICACID: Around North America with mefenamic acid", 20:104, 1978 November 17 (Box 437, Folder 93-97)
- "ARRHYTHMIAS: Bretylium (Bretylol) for ventricular arrhythmias", 20:105, 1978 December 1 (Box 437, Folder 98-102)
- "SMOKING: Aids for patients who want to stop Smoking", 20:107, 1978 December 1 (Box 438, Folder 103-108)
- "GLAUCOMA: Timolol maleate - a new drug for glaucoma", 20:109, 1978 December 15 (Box 438, Folder 109-111, Box 439, Folder 112-113)
- "DIAZOXIDE: Oral diazoxide for hypoglycemia", 20:110, 1978 December 15 (Box 439, Folder 114-119)
- "ANALGESICS: Butorphanol (Stadol), a new parenteral analgesic", 20:111, 1978 December 15 (Box 439, Folder 120-124, Box 440, Folder 125-126)
- "CORICOSTEROIDS, TOPICAL: one more topical corticosteroid", 20:112, 1978 December 15 (Box 440, Folder 127-131)
- "ARRHYTHMIAS: Treatment of cardiac arrhythmias", 20:113, 1978 December 29 (Box 440, Folder 132-134, Box 441, Folder 135-139)
- "RHEUMATISM & ARTHRITIS (CHEMOTHERAPY): Sulindac (Clinoril)- a new drug for arthritis", 21:1, 1979 January 12 (Box 441, Folder 140-144, Box 442, Folder 145)
- "LIPIDS (HEART DISEASE): High Density Lipoproteins (HDL)", 21:2, 1979 January 12 (Box 442, Folder 146-151)
- "AGING: Gerovital H3" Manufacturers' Replies, 21:4, 1979 January 12 (Box 442, Folder 152-155, Box 443, Folder 156-157)
- "DRUG INTERACTION: Adverse Interaction of drugs", 21:5, 1979 January 26 (Box 443, Folder 158-160)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Cefandole and Cefoxitin", 21:13, 1979 February 9 (Box 443, Folder 161-163, Box 444, Folder 164-166)
- "DOBUTAMINE: Dobutamine (Dobutrex)", 21:15, 1979 February 9 (Box 444, Folder 167-170)
- "VIRAL INFECTIONS (HERPES): Vidarabine for herpes simplex encephalitis" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:17, 1979 Feb. 23 (Box 444, Folder 171-173, Box 445, Folder 174-175)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE-OVERDOSE): Cocaine", 21:18, 1979 February 23 (Box 445, Folder 176-179)
- "MEDICAL EQUIPMENT & DEVICES: New Thermomenters", 21:29, 1979 Feb. 23 (Box 445, Folder 180-183, Box 446, Folder 184-186)
- "DRUGS and BREAST MILK: Update: drugs in breast milk", 21:21, 1979 March 9 (Box 446, Folder 187-189, Box 447, Folder 190-195)
- "ANTIHISTAMINES: Clemastine (Tavist) a new antihistamine", 21:24, "Peyronie's diseases with beta-blockers", 1979 March 9 (Box 447, Folder 196-200)
- "EPILEPSY: drugs for epilepsy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 21:25, 1979 March 23 (Box 448, Folder 201)
- "EPILEPSY: drugs for epilepsy" Original Manuscript, 21:25, 1979 April 6 (Box 448, Folder 202)
- "FOOD TOXICITY: Toxic reactions to plant products sold in health food stores", 21:29, 1979 April 6 (Box 448, Folder 203-208)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: Monistat, i.v.", 21:31, 1979 April 6 (Box 448, Folder 209-213)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: Cisplatin (Platinol)", 21:33, 1979 April 20 (Box 448, Folder 214-218)
- "TARDIVE DYSKINESIA: Prevention and treatment of tardive dyskinesia", 21:34, 1979 April 20 (Box 449, Folder 219-224)
- "CANCER TESTS: Hemoccult II", 21:36, 1979 April 20 (Box 449A, Folder 225-229)
- "PARKINSON'S DISEASE, CHEMOTHERAPY: Drugs for parkinsonism", 21:37, 1979 May 4 (Box 449A, Folder 230-234, Box 450, Folder 235)
- "FUNGAL INFECTION: Drugs for candida Infections of the skin and vagina", 21:39, 1979 May 4 (Box 450, Folder 236-242)
- "DIURETICS' Diulo", 21:40, 1979 May 4 (Box 450, Folder 243-247)
- "DIARRHEA: Travelers' Diarrhea", 21:41, 1979 May 18 (Box 451, Folder 248-251)
- "AGING: Drugs in the elderly", 21:43, 1979 May 18 (Box 451, Folder 252-256, Box 452, Folder 257-258)
- "PENNICILLINS, NEW (CARBENICILLIN): Promotion of carbenicillin for- Treatment of meningitis in children", 21:45, 1979 June 1 (Box 452, Folder 259-261)
- "SUNBURN: Sunscreen", 21:46, 1979 June 1 (Box 452, Folder 262-265, Box 453, Folder 266-267)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Thallium scans for evaluation of coronary heart disease", 21:49, 1979 June 15 (Box 453, Folder 268-273)
- "VITAMIN D: Calcitrol", 21:50, 1979 June 15 (Box 453, Folder 274-276, Box 454, Folder 277-279)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY: Guar gum, dietary fiber and diabetes" Consultants: ML Drafts: 21:51, 1979 June 15 (Box 454, Folder 280)
- MENINGITIS, NEOVATAL: Hazard of intraventricular antibiotics in neovatal- meningitis" & METHADONE: Methadone in breast milk 21:52, 1979 June 15 (Box 454, Folder 280)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY: Guar gum, dietary fiber and diabetes" Original Manuscript: 21:51, 1979 June 15 (Box 454, Folder 281)
- MENINGITIS, NEOVATAL: Hazard of intraventricular antibiotics in neovatal- meningitis" & METHADONE: Methadone in breast milk 21:52, 1979 June 15 (Box 454, Folder 281)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY: Guar gum, dietary fiber and diabetes" Reprints: 21:51, 1979 June 15 (Box 454, Folder 282)
- "MENINGITIS, NEOVATAL: Hazard of intraventricular antibiotics in neovatal- meningitis" & METHADONE: Methadone in breast milk 21:52, 1979 June 15 (Box 454, Folder 282)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY: Guar gum, dietary fiber and diabetes" Advertising: Package Insert, 21:51, 1979 June 15 (Box 454, Folder 283)
- "MENINGITIS, NEOVATAL: Hazard of intraventricular antibiotics in neovatal-meningitis" & METHADONE: Methadone in breast milk 21:52, 1979 June 29 (Box 454, Folder 283)
- "RUBELLA: The new rubella vaccine", 21:53, 1979 June 29 (Box 454, Folder 284-288)
- "LABORATORY TESTS: Effects of oral contraceptives on laboratory test results", 21:54, 1979 June 29 (Box 455, Folder 289-293)
- "IMMUNIZATION: Immunization for travelers", 21:57, 1979 July 13 (Box 455, Folder 294-297)
- "DIURETICS: Ticrynafen (Selacryn)", 21:61, 1979 July 27 (Box 456, Folder 298-302)
- "NUTRITION AND DIET: Vegetarian diets", 21:62, 1979 July 27 (Box 456, Folder 303-305, Box 457, Folder 306-308)
- "MYASTHENIA GRAVIS: Plasmapheresis for myasthenia garvis", 21:64, 1979 July 27 (Box 457, Folder 309-312)
- "OBESITY: A Nasal decongestant and a local anesthetic for weight control", 21:65, 1979 August 10 (Box 457, Folder 313-317)
- "GONOCOCCAL INFECTIONS: Treatment of gonorrhea", 21:66, 1979 August 10 (Box 458, Folder 318-322)
- "DIALYSIS: Home peritoneal dialysis for-stage renal disease", 21:69, 1979 August 24 (Box 458, Folder 323-326)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Ipecac syrup & activated charcoal- for treatment of poisoning in children", 21:70, 1979 August 24 (Box 458, Folder 327-329, Box 459, Folder 330-332)
- "MALARIA: Chemoprophylasis of Chloroquine resistant malaria: an additional note", 21:72, 1979 August 24 (Box 459, Folder 333-335)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Antimicrobial prophylaxis for Surgery", 21:73, 1979 September 7 (Box 459, Folder 336-338, Box 460, Folder 339-341)
- "PROPRANOLOL: Propranolol for prevention of migraine headaches", 21:77, 1979 September 21 (Box 460, Folder 342-346)
- "LITHIUM: Lithium for cluster headache", 21:78, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 347-350)
- "EYE DISEASE: Natamycin for keratomycosis", 21:79, 1979 September 21 (Box 461, Folder 351-354)
- "MENSTRUATION, DISORDERS: Drugs for dysmenorrheal", 21:81, 1979 October 5 (Box 461, Folder 355-356, Box 462, Folder 357-361)
- "ANALGSICS: Nalbuphine", 21:83, 1979 October 5 (Box 462, Folder 362-366)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Two new oral cephalosporins", 21:85, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 367, 367A, 368-372)
- "ANGINA PECTORIS: Oral isosorbide dinitrate for angina", 21:88, 1979 October 19 (Box 463, Folder 373-376)
- "METRONIDAZOLE: Metronidazole (Flagyl)", 21:89, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 377-381)
- "CANCER TESTS: Early detection of prostatic cancer by radioimmunoassay for Prostatic acid phosphate", 21:90, 1979 November 2 (Box 464, Folder 382-386)
- "FEET: Corrective shoes for infants and children", 21:91, 1979 November 2 (Box 465, Folder 387-391)
- "BLOOD PRODUCTS: Blood Products", 21:93, 1979 November 16 (Box 465, Folder 392-398)
- "COLITIS: Antibiotic colitis - new cause, new treatment", 21:97, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 399-403)
- "POISONS AND POISONING: Acetylcysteine for acetylcysteine overdose", 21:98, 1979 November 30 (Box 466, Folder 404, Box 467, Folder 405-408)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE, OVERDOSE): Clonidine for opiate withdrawal", 21:100, 1979 November 30 (Box 467, Folder 409-413)
- "BETA-ADRENERGIC BLOCKERS: Beta-blockers after myocardial infarction", 21:101, 1979 December 14 (Box 467, Folder 414-417, Box 468, Folder 418)
- "MEASLES: Measles vaccine for adolescents and young adults", 21:102, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 419-423)
- "ANTITUSSIVES: Over the counter cough remedies", 21:104, 1979 December 14 (Box 468, Folder 424-428)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUG FOR): Drugs for parasitic infections", 21:105, 1979 December 28 (Box 469, Folder 429-434)
- "DISULFIRAM (ANTABUSE): Disulfiram (Antabuse)", 22:1, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 435-439)
- "LAXATIVES & CATHARTICS: Lactulose (Chronulac) for constipation", 22:2, 1980 January 11 (Box 470, Folder 440-444)
- "HYDROXYZINE: Atara (hydroxyzine) for itching", 22:4, 1980 January 11 (Box 471, Folder 445-449)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS: The Choice of antimicrobial drugs", 22:5, 1980 January 25 (Box 471, Folder 450-452, Box 472, Folder 453-456)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Cyclacillin (Cyclapen) - another new penicillin", 22:13, 1980 February 8 (Box 472, Folder 457-462)
- "HYPERTENSION THERAPY: Salt restriction to prevent hypertension", 22:14, 1980 February 8 (Box 472, Folder 463-464, Box 473, Folder 465-467)
- "DEPRESSION, THERAPY (TRIMIPRAMINE): Trimipramine maleate- (Surmontil) - another tricyclic antidepressant", 22:16, 1980 February 8 (Box 473, Folder 468-473)
- "LITHIUM: Another look at lithium", 22:17, 1980 February 22 (Box 473, Folder 474-475, Box 474, Folder 476-481)
- "VITAMINS, A: Vitamin A toxicity", 22:19, 1980 February 22 (Box 474, Folder 482, Box 475, Folder 483-487)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Minoxidil (Loniten)", 22:21, 1980 March 7 (Box 475, Folder 488-493, Box 476, Folder 494-497)
- "HEART DISEASE, MYOCARDIAL INFRACTION: Antiplatlet drugs after myocardial Infraction", 22:25, 1980 March 21 (Box 476, Folder 498-499, Box 477, Folder 500-503)
- "GASTROINTESTINAL SYSTEM DISEASE: Drugs for esophageal reflux", 22:26, 1980 March 21 (Box 477, Folder 504-508)
- "PHEOCHROMOCYTOMA: Metyrosine for pheochromocytoma", 22:28, 1980 March 21 (Box 477, Folder 509-512, Box 478, Folder 513)
- "RHEUMATISM AND ARTHRITIS, CHEMOTHERAPY: Nonsteroidal- anti-inflammatory drugs for rheumatoid arthritis", 22:29, 1980 April 4 (Box 478, Folder 514-521)
- "SKIN DISEASE, THERAPY: Drugs for acne", 22:31, 1980 April 4 (Box 478, Folder 522, Box 479, Folder 523-526)
- "BETA-ADRENERGIC BLOCKERS: Nadolol (Corgard) - a new beta blocker", 22:33, 1980 April 18 (Box 479, Folder 527-531, Box 480, Folder 532-534)
- "LEUKEMIA: Daunorubicin (Cerubine)", 22:34, 1980 April 18 (Box 480, Folder 535-540)
- "NITROFURANTOIN: Nitrofurantoin", 22:36, 1980 April 18 (Box 481, Folder 541-545)
- "INSECT BITES and STINGS: Insect-venom extracts", 22:37, 1980 May 2 (Box 481, Folder 546-550)
- "CORTICOSTEROIDS, TOPICAL: Topical hydrocortisone without a prescription", 22:38, 1980 May 2 (Box 481, Folder 551, Box 482, Folder 552-556)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Captopril for hypertension", 22:39, 1980 May 2 (Box 482, Folder 557-560)
- "MARIJUANA: Marijuana for nausea & vomiting due to cancer chemotherapy", 22:41, 1980 May 16 (Box 482, Folder 561, Box 483, Folder 562-564)
- "PLASTICS: Plastic containers for intravenous solutions", 22:43, 1980 May 16 (Box 483, Folder 565-571)
- "OSTEOPOROSTS: Drugs for postmenopausal osteoporosts", 22:45, 1980 May 30 (Box 484, Folder 572-576)
- "VIRAL INFECTION (HERPES): Trifluridine (Viroptic) for herpetic keratitis, 22:46, 1980 May 30 (Box 484, Folder 577-579, Box 485, Folder 580-581)
- "BROMOCRIPTINE: Bromocriptine to prevent lactation", 22:48, 1980 May 30 (Box 485, Folder 582-586)
- "ULTRASOUND: Ultrasound for aches & pains", Never Published, 1980 May (Box 485, Folder 587-589, Box 486, Folder 590)
- "PHENYTOIN: Dilantin generic phenytoin sodium", 22:49, 1980 June 13 (Box 486, Folder 591-596)
- "PARKINSON'S DISEASE, LEVODOPA (COMBINED THERAPY: Sinemet-25/100", 22:51, 1980 June 13 (Box 486, Folder 597-601)
- "CORTICOSTEROIDS, TROPICAL: Amcinonide (Cyclocort) - a new topical corticosteroid", 22:51, 1980 June 13 (Box 487, Folder 602-608)
- "CANCER TESTS: Mammography screening for breast cancer", 22:53, 1980 June 27 (Box 487, Folder 609-614)
- DEPRESSION THERAY: (TRICYCLICS): Physostigmine for tricyclic antidepressant overdosage", 22:55, 1980 June 27 (Box 488, Folder 615-620)
- "CONTRAST MEDIA: Amipaque - a new contrast medium for myelography", 22:56, 1980 June 27 (Box 488, Folder 621-626)
- "ESTROGENS: Quinestrol (Estrovis) for estrogen replacement", 22:57, 1980 July 11 (Box 488, Folder 627, Box 489, Folder 628-632)
- "DEPRESSION, THERAPY: Monoamine oxidase inhibitors for depression", 22:58, 1980 July 11 (Box 489, Folder 633-634, Box 490, Folder 635-638)
- "DANTROLENE: Dantrolene for malignant hyperthermia during anesthesia", 22:61, 1980 July 25 (Box 490, Folder 639-643)
- "SALICYLATES: Salicylate in Pepto-Bismol", 22:63, 1980 July 25 (Box 490, Folder 644-649)
- "PHOTOSENSITIVITY: Photosensitivity from drugs, perfumes and cosmetics", 22:64, 1980 July 25 (Box 491, Folder 650-654)
- LIPIDS, DRUGS REDUCTION: Lipid-lowering drugs", 22:65, 1980 August 8 (Box 491, Folder 655-658)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (DRUGS FOR): Treatment of head lice", 22:66, 1980 August 8 (Box 492, Folder 659-664)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLATIC USE (RESPIRATORY DISEASE): Antibiotics in chronic bronchitis", 22:68, 1980 August 8 (Box 492, Folder 665-668, Box 493, Folder 669-671)
- "TRIMETHOPRIM: Trimethoprim", 22:69, 1980 August 22 (Box 493, Folder 672-675)
- "ASPRIN: Asprin for transient ischemic attacks", 22:71, 1980 August 22 (Box 493, Folder 676-678, Box 494, Folder 679-680)
- "PLANTS, MEDICINAL: Ginseng", 22:72, 1980 August 22 (Box 494, Folder 681-685)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE-OVERDOSE): Diagnosis and management- of reactions to drug abuse", 22:73, 1980 September 5 (Box 494, Folder 686, Box 495, Folder 687-692)
- "PSYCHOPHARMACOLOGICAL AGENTS: Drugs for psychiatric disorders", 22:77, 1980 September 19 (Box 496, Folder 693-698, Box 497, Folder 699-700)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, SIDE EFFECTS: Gemtamicin vs. tobramycin", 22:85, 1980 October 3 (Box 497, Folder 701-706)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES, INTRAUTERINE: Another look at IUDs", 22:86, 1980 October 3 (Box 497, Folder 707-708, Box 498, Folder 709-712)
- "PREGNANCY: Ritodrine for inhibition of pre=term labor", 22:89, 1980 October 17 (Box 498, Folder 713-716)
- "CONTRACEPTIVES: Topical spermicides for contraception", 22:90, 1980 October 17 (Box 499, Folder 717-723)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1980-1981", 22:91, 1980 October 17 (Box 499, Folder 724, Box 500, Folder 725-728)
- "RABIES: Human diploid cell rabies vaccine", 22:93, 1980 October 31 (Box 499, Folder 729-733)
- "DIMETHYL SULFOXIDE: Dimethyl sulfoxide", 22:94, 1980 October 31 (Box 500, Folder 734-740)
- "CHLORAMPHENICOL" Chloramphenicol ophthalmic formulations", 22:96, 1980 October 31 (Box 501, Folder 741-744)
- "EYE DISEASE: Radial keratotomy-an operation for myopia", 22:97, 1980 November 14 (Box 501, Folder 745-747)
- "BLOOD: Eligibility for blood donation", 22:98, 1980 November 14 (Box 501, Folder 748-749, Box 502, Folder 750-752)
- "OBESITY, DRUGS FOR: Fructose for weight reduction", 22:100, 1980 November 14 (Box 502, Folder 753-758)
- "CANCER CHEMOTHERAPY: Cancer chemotherapy", 22:101, 1980 November 28 (Box 502, Folder 759, Box 503, Folder 760-768)
- "SKIN DISEASE: New Topical antibiotics for acne", 22:107, 1980 December 12 (Box 503, Folder 769-770, Box 504, Folder 771-774)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause sexual dysfunction", 22:108, 1980 December 12 (Box 504, Folder 775-778, Box 505, Folder 779-780)
- "RHEUMATISM AND ARTHRITIS, CHEMOTHERAPY: Meclofenamate sodium (Meclomen) - a new antiarthritic agent", 22:111, 1980 December 26 (Box 505, Folder 781-787)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Treatment of frostbite", 22:112, 1980 December 26 (Box 505, Folder 788-789, Box 506, Folder 790-791)
- "IMMUNIZATIONS (VACCINES): Pneumococcal vaccine", 22:114, 1980 December 26 (Box 506, Folder 792-796)
- "ANALGESICS: Zomepirac Sodium - a new oral analgesic", 23:1, 1981 January 5 (Box 506, Folder 797-803)
- "POTASSIUM: Klotrix and other slow release potassium tablets", 23:3, 1981 January 5 (Box 507, Folder 804-808)
- "DANAZOL: Danazol for fibrocystic disease of the breast", 23:5, 1981 January 23 (Box 507, Folder 809-815)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Medical problems at high altitudes", 23:7, 1981 January 23 (Box 508, Folder 816-820)
- "DRUGS, INJURIOUS EFFECTS: Drugs that cause psychiatric symptoms", 23:9, 1981 February 6 (Box 508, Folder 821-823, Box 509, Folder 824-829)
- "METRONIDAZOLE: Metronidazole Hydrochloride (Flagyl I.V.)", 23:13, 1981 February 20 (Box 509, Folder 830, Box 510, Folder 831-836)
- "HAIR: Treatment of hirsutism", 23:15, 1981 May 1 (Box 510, Folder 837-843)
- "HAIR: Electrolysis for hirsutism: an additional note", 23:44, 1981 February 20 (Box 510, Folder 837-843)
- "SHOCK THERAPY: Hetastarch (Hespan) - a new plasma expander", 23:16, 1981 February 20 (Box 511, Folder 844-849)
- "VERAPAMIL: Verapamil for arrhythmias", 23:29, 1981 March 20 (Box 511, Folder 850-854)
- "THYROID FUNCTION TESTS: Effects of drugs on thyroid function tests", 23:30 and Correction, 23:52, 1981 March-May (Box 512, Folder 855-861)
- "DRUG INTERACTIONS: Interactions of drugs with alcohol", 23:33, 1981 April 3 (Box 512, Folder 862-864)
- "BONE: Electrical stimulators to promote bone healing", 23:35, 1981 April 3 (Box 512, Folder 865, Box 513, Folder 866-872)
- "MENINGITIS: Preventing spread of meningococcal disease", 23:37, 1981 April 17 (Box 513, Folder 873-874)
- "PAPAVERINE: Pavabid HP", 23:38, 1981 April 17 (Box 514, Folder 875-879)
- "AMOXAPINE: Amoxapine (Asendin) - a new antidepressant", 23:39, 1981 April 17 (Box 514, Folder 880-886)
- "BENZODIAZEPINES: Choice of benzodiazepines", 23:41 and Correction, 23:60, 1981 May and June (Box 514, Folder 887, Box 515, Folder 888-895)
- "DIAGNOSTIC TESTS: Counterimmunaelestrophoresis (CIE) for rapid diagnosis of bacteremia and bacterial meningitis", 23:43, 1981 May 1 (Box 516, Folder 896-899)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension", 23:45, 1981 May 15 (Box 516, Folder 900-901)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Bacampicillin hydrochloride (Spectrobid)", 23:49, 1981 May 29 (Box 516, Folder 902-907, Box 517, Folder 908-910)
- "CARDIOVASCULAR DISEASE, THERAPY: EDTA Chelation therapy for arteriosclerotic heart disease", 23:51, 1981 May 29 (Box 517, Folder 911-915)
- "LAXATIVES AND CATHARTICS: Calcium Polycarbophil (Mitrolan)", 23:52, 1981 May 29 (Box 517, Folder 916-920)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY (INSULIN): Purified insulin preparation", 23:53, 1981 June 12 (Box 518, Folder 921-925)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE: Antimicrobial Prophylaxis and treatment in patients with granulocytopenia", 23:55 and Correction, 23:68, 1981 June 12; July 24 1981 (Box 518, Folder 926-930)
- "URINARY TRACT INFECTIONS (Treatment): Cinoxacin (Cinobac) - a new drug for urinary tract infection", 23:57, 1981 June 26 (Box 518, Folder 931, Box 519, Folder 932-936)
- "MAPROTILINE: Maprotiline (Ludiomil) - another antidepressant", 23:58, 1981 June 26 (Box 519, Folder 937-943)
- "CANCER: Treatment of Malignant pleural and pericardial effusions", 23:59, 1981 June 26 (Box 520, Folder 944-947)
- "CEPHALOSPORINS: Cefotaxime Sodium (Claforan)", 23:61, 1981 July 10 (Box 520, Folder 948-953)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Exertional heat injury", 23:63, 1981 July 10 (Box 521, Folder 954-959)
- "ASPIRIN: Aspirin products", 23:65, 1981 July 24 (Box 521, Folder 960-961, Box 522, Folder 962-967)
- "LACTOSE INTOLERANCE: Treatment of lactose intolerance", 23:67, 1981 July 24 (Box 522, Folder 968-970, Box 523, Folder 971-974)
- "URINARY TRACT INFECTION: Treatment of urinary tract infection", 23:69, 1981 August 7 (Box 523, Folder 975-979)
- "AMINOGLUTETHIMIDE: Aminoglutethimide", 23:71, 1981 August 7 (Box 524, Folder 980-986)
- "MENINGITIS: New drugs for enteric gram-negative bacillary- meningitis in adults", 23:73, 1981 August 21 (Box 524, Folder 987-989, Box 525, Folder 990-991)
- "ANESTHETIC: Innovar: a follow-up", 23:74, 1981 August 21 (Box 525, Folder 992-996)
- "ANALGESICS: Prostaglandin - inhibitor analgesics", 23:75, 1981 August 21 (Box 525, Folder 997-1000, Box 526, Folder 1001-1004)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Treatment of heat stroke", Consultants: ML Drafts, 23:76, 1981 September 4 (Box 526, Folder 1005)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLAXIS, SURGERY: Antimicrobial prophylaxis for surgery", 23:77, 1981 September 4 (Box 526, Folder 1006-1008, Box 527, Folder 1009-1010)
- "ALBUTEROL: Albuterol", 23:81, 1981 September 18 (Box 527, Folder 1011-1019)
- "NITROGLYCERIN: Nitroglycerin ointment for angina pectoris", 23:82, 1981 September 18 (Box 528, Folder 1020-1025)
- "DANAZOL: Danazol and other androgens for hereditary angioedema", 23:83, 1981 September 18 (Box 528, Folder 1026-1030, Box 529, Folder 1031-1033)
- "KETOCONAZOLE: Ketoconazole (Nizoral) a new antifungal agent", 23:85, 1981 October 2 (Box 529, Folder 1034-1039, Box 530, Folder 1040)
- "AZATHIOPRINE: Azathioprine (Imuran) for rheumatoid arthritis", 23:87, 1981 October 2 (Box 530, Folder 1041-1047)
- "SCOPOLMINE: Transdermal scopolamine for notion sickness", 23:89, 1981 October 16 (Box 531, Folder 1048-1053)
- "NITROUS OXIDE: Nitrous oxide for painful procedures", 23:90, 1981 October 16 (Box 531, Folder 1054-1057)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE ( ENDOCARDITIS): Prevention of bacterial endocarditis", 23:90, and Correction, 23:104, 1981 October 16; November 27 1981 (Box 531, Folder 1058-1059)
- "OTITIS MEDIA: Antimicrobial agents for acute otitis media", 23:93, 1981 October 30 (Box 532, Folder 1060-1067)
- "INDOMETHACIN: Indomethacin for patent ductus arteriosus", and "Indomethacin available as solution for patent ductus", 23:104 and 23:95, 1981 October-November (Box 532, Folder 1068, Box 533, Folder 1069-1074)
- "THEOPHYLLINE: Sustained-release theophylline", 23:97, 1981 November 13 (Box 533, Folder 1075-1076, Box 534, Folder 1077-1084, Box 535, Folder 1085-1089)
- "INFLUENZA: Influenza prevention for 1981-1982", 23:99, 1981 November 13 (Box 535, Folder 1090-1093)
- "PRAMOXINE: Tronolane (Pramoxine)", 23:100, 1981 November 13 (Box 536, Folder 1094-1102)
- "CORTICOSTEROIDS: Intranasal corticosteroid aerosols for noninfectious rhinitis", 23:101, 1981 November 27 (Box 537, Folder 1103-1110)
- "TRIMETHOPRIM - SULFAMETHOXAZOLE: Trimethoprim - Sulfamethoxazole- for intravenous infusion", 23:102, 1981 November 27 (Box 538, Folder 1111-1115)
- "LACRISERT: Lacrisert", 23:104, 1981 November 27 (Box 538, Folder 1116-1118, Box 539, Folder 1119-1120)
- "IMMUNIZATION: Immunizations and chemoprophylaxis for travelers", 23:105, 1981 December 11 (Box 539, Folder 1121-1125)
- "AMILORIDE: Amiloride - a potassium-sparing diuretic", 23:109, 1981 December 25 (Box 540, Folder 1126-1131)
- "MEZLOCILLIN: Mezlocillin Sodium (Mezin)", 23:110, 1981 December 25 (Box 540, Folder 1132-1135, Box 541, Folder 1136-1137)